Start the message broker and connect to a FoxMQ cluster

Usage: foxmq.exe run [OPTIONS] [CONFIG_DIR]

Arguments:
  [CONFIG_DIR]
          The directory containing `address-book.toml` and (optionally) `users.toml`
          
          [default: foxmq.d/]

Options:
  -l, --log <LOG>
          Set the format of log output
          
          [default: full]

          Possible values:
          - full:    Emit human-readable single line logs for each event
          - compact: A variant of full, optimized for shorter line lengths
          - pretty:  Format events in multi-line very "prettified" form
          - json:    Emit JSON-lines formatted events

  -L, --mqtt-addr <MQTT_ADDR>
          The TCP socket address to listen for MQTT (non-TLS) connections from clients
          
          [default: 0.0.0.0:1883]

  -C, --cluster-addr <CLUSTER_ADDR>
          The UDP socket address to listen for cluster connections from other FoxMQ brokers
          
          [default: 0.0.0.0:19793]

      --max-keep-alive <MAX_KEEP_ALIVE>
          Set the maximum Keep Alive interval for MQTT connections, in seconds.
          
          A client may specify a nonzero interval smaller than this. This also becomes the default Keep Alive interval if a client does not specify one.
          
          Per the specification, the connection times out if the client does not send any MQTT control packet in 1.5x the Keep Alive interval.
          
          Set to 0 to allow the client to set any Keep Alive interval, including 0 (no timeout).
          
          The maximum value allowed by the MQTT spec is 65,535, or 18 hours, 12 minutes, and 15 seconds.
          
          [default: 3600]

      --allow-anonymous-login
          Allow clients to authenticate without providing user credentials

      --silent-connect-errors
          If enabled, don't respond if CONNECT handling (including authentication) for a client fails.
          
          This can be used to avoid advertising that an MQTT broker is running on the given port, which makes it harder to categorize in a port scanning attack and identify as a potential target.
          
          By default, a response is sent to the client detailing the reason why the handshake failed.
          
          If enabled, the error is simply logged at DEBUG level and the socket is silently closed.

  -k, --secret-key <SECRET_KEY>
          Read the P-256 secret key used to identify this broker in the cluster from hex encoded DER.
          
          If `--tls-key-file` is not provided and `--mqtts` is enabled, this or `--secret-key-file` will be used by default.
          
          [env: SECRET_KEY=]

  -f, --secret-key-file <SECRET_KEY_FILE>
          Read the PEM-encoded P-256 secret key used to identify this broker in the cluster from a file
          
          [env: SECRET_KEY_FILE=]

      --mqtts
          Enable listening for MQTT-over-TLS connections on a separate socket (0.0.0.0:8883 by default)

      --mqtts-addr <MQTTS_ADDR>
          The TCP socket address to listen for MQTT-over-TLS (`mmqts`) connections from clients
          
          [default: 0.0.0.0:8883]

      --server-name <SERVER_NAME>
          The domain name to report for Server Name Identification (SNI) in TLS
          
          [default: foxmq.local]

      --tls-key-file <TLS_KEY_FILE>
          Override the secret key used for TLS handshakes.
          
          Note: this only applies to MQTT-over-TLS connections (`--mqtts`).
          
          Defaults to the main secret key (`--secret-key`/`--secret-key-file`).

      --tls-cert-file <TLS_CERT_FILE>
          Path to the X.509 certificate to use for TLS.
          
          Note: this only applies to MQTT-over-TLS connections  (`--mqtts`).
          
          Defaults to a certificate self-signed with either `--tls-key-file` or the main secret key (`--secret-key`/`--secret-key-file`).

      --websockets
          Enable listening for MQTT-over-Websockets connections on a separate socket (0.0.0.0:8080 by default)

      --websockets-addr <WEBSOCKETS_ADDR>
          The TCP socket address to listen for MQTT-over-Websockets (`ws`) connections from clients
          
          [default: 0.0.0.0:8080]

      --cluster-cert <CLUSTER_CERT>
          Path to a TLS certificate or certificate chain file to present to peers on new cluster connections.
          
          If not set, a self-signed TLS certificate is generated on startup.
          
          If set, the certificate _must_ match the secret key specified by `--secret-key` or `--secret-key-path`.
          
          [env: CLUSTER_CERT=]

      --cluster-root-cert <CLUSTER_ROOT_CERT>
          Path to a TLS root certificate file to use for cluster operations.
          
          If set, all peers must present a valid TLS certificate chain that ends with this certificate.
          
          [env: CLUSTER_ROOT_CERT=]

      --cluster-accept-peer-with-cert
          If set, admit any peer to the cluster that connects with a valid TLS certificate.
          
          This allows peers to connect even if they aren't in the initial address book.
          
          A valid certificate is any certificate chain that ends with the certificate specified by `--cluster-root-cert`.
          
          [env: CLUSTER_ACCEPT_PEER_WITH_CERT=]

  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')
